<?xml version="1.0"?>
<module>
<name>Module 1</name>
<section type="text">
	<name>Integrity Defined</name>
	<body>
		According to the Oxford English Dictionary, integrity, in a moral sense, is:
		Soundness of moral principle; the character of uncorrupted virtue, especially in relation to truth and fair dealing; uprightness, honesty, sincerity.
		Try not to become a man of success. Rather become a man of value.
		- Albert Einstein (1879 – 1955)
	</body>
	<image>Assets/einstein.jpg</image>
</section>
<section type="text">
	<name>A person of integrity</name>
	<body>
		A person of integrity is aware of, and sensitive to, the needs of others. They strive to identify the right action in all situations and everyday behaviour. Possible actions are weighed and prioritized in view of ends that serve society not just individuals.

		Personal integrity is a goal in progress, and a life-long commitment.

		If everyone were clothed with integrity, if every heart were just, frank, and kindly, the other virtues would be well-nigh useless, since their chief purpose is to make us bear with patience the injustice of our fellows. - Molière
	</body>
	<image>Assets/moliere.jpg</image>
</section>
<section type="text">
	<name>Challenges and rewards of integrity</name>
	<body>
		The rewards of integrity are substantial, for the individual and the community. A person of integrity enjoys the self-respect that comes from honestly earned accomplishments and contributions to the larger good.

		However, acting with integrity comes with challenges. We may not always be aware of the needs of others, particularly individuals at a distance. The rewards of moral behaviour are often not immediate or apparent. It may seem as though the right thing to do has few benefits in comparison with an action that could bring immediate gain.

		An individual who aspires to strong moral standards experiences the rewards of personal satisfaction and the affirmation of belonging to a community of integrity.

		Real integrity is doing the right thing, knowing that nobody's going to know whether you did it or not. - Oprah Winfrey
	</body>
	<image>Assets/oprah.jpg</image>
</section>
<section type="video">
	<name>Some birds</name>
	<video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/QVGeilNsJFU</video>
</section>
</module>