<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<quiz>
	<title>Check your understanding</title>
	<body>
		This section will test your understanding of the concepts and issues presented in the tutorial. It is divided into four sections and should take about 5 to 10 minutes to complete.

		For each question, select a response and then check your answer. If your response was not correct, try again. Check your response to each question separately; your answers are not retained from one question to the next.
	</body>
	<questions>
		<question>
			<text>Which of the following are fundamental values of academic integrity?</text>
			<options>
				<option>
					<answer>Honesty</answer>
					<explanation>
						Your answer is partially correct. Lying in all matters concerning your academic communications, including exams and assignments, is academic misconduct.

						However, the best answer is "all of the above."

						These values are all fundamental to academic integrity:

						honesty
						trust
						fairness
						respect
						responsibility
						Try again!
					</explanation>
				</option>
				<option>
					<answer>Trust</answer>
					<explanation>
						Your answer is partially correct. A trustworthy person can be believed in;
						they present themselves and their work without deception.

						However, the best answer is "all of the above."

						These values are all fundamental to academic integrity:

						honesty
						trust
						fairness
						respect
						responsibility
						Try again!
					</explanation>
				</option>
				<option>
					<answer>Fairness</answer>
					<explanation>
						Incorrect:
						Your answer is partially correct. It is academic misconduct to facilitate unfair advantage through actions such as posting assignment solutions to discussion boards, letting a classmate sneak a peek at your answers during an exam, or giving classmates copies of your assignment.

						However, the best answer is "all of the above."

						These values are all fundamental to academic integrity:

						honesty
						trust
						fairness
						respect
						responsibility
						Try again!
					</explanation>
				</option>
				<option>
					<answer>Respect</answer>
					<explanation>
						Incorrect:
						Your answer is partially correct. Inappropriate, disrespectful behaviour undermines a culture of academic integrity.

						However, the best answer is "all of the above."

						These values are all fundamental to academic integrity:

						honesty
						trust
						fairness
						respect
						responsibility
						Try again!
					</explanation>
				</option>
				<option>
					<answer>Responsibility</answer>
					<explanation>
						Incorrect:
						Your answer is partially correct. Waterloo students have a responsibility to conform to standards acceptable in the University of Waterloo community.

						However, the best answer is "all of the above."

						These values are all fundamental to academic integrity:

						honesty
						trust
						fairness
						respect
						responsibility
						Try again!
					</explanation>
				</option>
				<option>
					<answer correct="true">All of the Above</answer>
					<explanation>
						Correct!
						Your answer is correct. These values are all fundamental to academic integrity.

						Honesty: Lying in all matters concerning your academic communications
						is academic misconduct.
						Trust: A trustworthy person can be believed in; trustworthy people
						present themselves and their work without deception.
						Fairness: It is academic misconduct to facilitate unfair advantage
						Respect: Inappropriate, disrespectful behaviour undermines a culture of
						academic integrity.
						Responsibility: Waterloo students have a responsibility to conform to standards acceptable in the community.

						Next question:
					</explanation>
				</option>
			</options>
		</question>
		<question>
			<text>The University of Waterloo has a policy that describes the offences that constitute misconduct.</text>
			<options>
				<option>
					<answer correct="true">True</answer>
					<explanation>
						University Policy 71 - Student Discipline describes offences that constitute misconduct. It also outlines what penalties apply.

						You should be familiar with this policy, and Policy 72 - Student Appeals.

						Next question:
					</explanation>
				</option>
				<option>
					<answer>False</answer>
					<explanation>
						Incorrect:
						The offences that constitute misconduct are described in University
						Policy 71 - Student Discipline.

						Try again!
					</explanation>
				</option>
			</options>
		</question>
	</questions>
</quiz>